>> Brian Holt: 让我们谈谈上下文是什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's talk
about what context is.
在这个课程的第一个版本中，我根本没有教过任何内容，
In the first versions of this course
I didn't teach context at all,
因为它是一个不稳定的 API
because it used to be an unstable API.
此课程中的第四个课程作为一个稳定的 API 来实现，因此
With version four of this course
it landed as a stable API and so
它现在其实是你有时候想用的东西。
it's actually now something that
you might want to use sometimes.
所以，让我们谈谈为什么它可能有用。
So, let's talk about why it
could potentially be useful.
有时您会像全局应用程序状态一样
Sometimes you'll have like
global applications state and
一个很好的例子就是用户登录信息。
a really good example of this would be
something like user log in information.
所以，也许你在 Netflix.com 当一个用户从路线浏览到
So, maybe you are in Netflix.com and
as a user navigates from route to route to
路由，每个页面都将使用该用户的数据。
route, every single page is gonna
use pieces of that user's data.
您应该在此处显示电子邮件，
You should display the email here,
你在这里展示他们的用户喜好
you show them their user
preferences over here,
向他们显示您将从用户登录所获得的所有信息。
you show them all this information that
you would get from the user logging in.
现在我给你展示的所有工具
Right now with all the tools
that I've shown you,
你要做的就是把所有信息都放进应用程序点 JS
what you would do is you'd put all
the information into app dot JS and
你就会把它传给每个孩子
you would just pass it
into every single child.
然后你就会有这个问题我们称之为道具钻井
Then, you would kind of have this
problem we would call prop drilling
如果你要把父母的财产交给孩子
where you would have to take the property
from the parent, pass it into the child,
从父代获取属性，将其传递到子代。
take the property from the parent,
pass it into the child.
所以在多个层面上，都是很烦人的。
So on and so forth down multiple levels,
it's annoying.
它也很有用，因为您可以通过应用程序查看数据流，但是
It's also useful because you can see the
flow of data through your application, but
在任何地方都要为用户数据做任何事情都是很烦人的
it's annoying to have to do it
everywhere for something like user data,
因为应用程序的每个部分都将联系您的用户数据。
because every part of your application
is going to touch your user data.
你知道这有什么问题吗
You kind of get where this is the problem?
我们一直在用雷德克斯来解决这个问题。
Where we have been solving that
is using redux, historically.
Redux 通常是您在旁边有此数据存储器。
Redux is typically you have
this data store on the side and
您将所有信息输入到数据存储器中，
you feed all the information
into the data store and
那么应用程序的每个部分都可以从 redux 存储中读取。
then every part of your application
can read from the redux store.
Redux 很难
Redux is hard.
我们会在中间的反应中进行
We'll actually go over it
in intermediate React, but
这类事情很难而且经常会被过度杀戮
it's hard and often overkill for
these sort of things.
还有一件新事物是你可以使用的叫做 " 上下文 " 的新事物
There's another thing that's new to
React called Context that you can use,
你可以把这些都加载到
that you can load these into basically
整个 React 应用程序可以使用和更新的数据存储器。
a data store that your entire React
application can use and update.
但知道那是一把双刃剑对吧
But just know that's kind of
a double edged sword, right?
你在利用 React 的明显优势
You're taking out the advantage
of React of being explicit, and
现在一切都是隐性的，对吧 ?
now everything kind of has
implicit dependencies, right?
这很困难
It's hard.
那么让我们， >> Brian Holt: 我们去看看
So let's,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's go take a look
你是怎么做到的
at how you do that.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我希望您在此创建新的文件
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
I want you to make a new file here and
我要你把它叫做 ThemeContex.js
I want you to call it ThemeContext.js.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，这里很短，很甜。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
gonna be short and sweet here.
我们要为申请做个主题
We're gonna make a theme for
our application.
因此，导入，创建上下文，从反应开始。
So import, create context, from react.
>> Brian Holt: 我将说 const ThemeContext = React.createContext 和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'm gonna say const
ThemeContext = React.createContext and
我们会给它一个钩状的形状
we're gonna give it a hook-like shape,
因为我们要在里面贴个钩子
because we're actually going to
stick a hook inside of here.
但是你知道，你可以在上下文中做任何事情。
But just so you know,
you can stick anything in context.
它可以是一个对象，它可以是函数，它可以是一个字符串，一个数字，
It can be an object, it can be function,
it can be a string, a number,
不管你想要什么
whatever you want.
但我们实际上是要在那里贴一个钩子。
But we're actually going to
literally stick a hook in there.
所以我们要放绿色
So, we're gonna put green, or
任何您喜欢的 CSS 名称和功能。
whatever your favorite CSS name color is,
and a function.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，我为什么会得到这个空函数?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now,
why did I get this empty function?
这实际上是一个占位符，所以它会使用这个特殊的
This is actually a placeholder,
so it will use this particular
如果它没有上面的提供程序，但它永远不应该发生。
function if it has no provider above
it but this should never happen.
这对你未来的自我是更公正的说明。
So this is actually more just notes for
your future self.
这就是这看起来的样子，这才是钩子的样子。
This is what this looks like and
this is what a hook looks like.
它有国家，有一个更新者。
It has the state and it has an updater.
在这种情况下，更新者什么都不做，所以
In this case,
the updater doesn't do anything, so
我们只是给它一个空虚的功能
we just give it an empty function.
>> Brian Holt: 有意义吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Make sense?
我们不想要 React.createContext。
And we don't want React.createContext.
我们只需要这样的 createContext 。
We just want createContext like that.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，然后在下面下面，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
then down here at the bottom,
仅导出缺省 ThemeContext。
just export default ThemeContext.
> > Brian Holt: 现在我们创建了上下文，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
now we've created the context,
现在我们要把它用在我们的 app.js里
now we're gonna go use
it inside of our app.js.
好吗 ? 不需要 app.js
Okay?
Instead of app.js we want
您要导入 themeContext
you to import themeContext
来自 /themeContext。
from /themeContext.
在我们要创建的应用程序中，我们也需要使用状态来进行反应。
Here inside of app we're going to create,
we also need use state from react.
所以请从这里开始使用状态。
So get use state from up here.
使用状态。
Use state.
>> Brian Holt: 我们会说， >> Brian Holt: Const
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we're gonna say,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Const
themeHook = useState。
themeHook = useState.
我们必须给它一些默认值。
And we have to give it
some default values.
因此，要显示缺省值不同，
So just to show that
the default value is different,
我要把深蓝色放在这里
I'm gonna put dark blue in here.
> > Brian Holt: 现在记住我们通常都在做，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now remember
we normally have been doing,
>> Brian Holt: 此处的颜色和 setColor 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: color and setColor here.
就像这里的钩子如果你还记得以前的事
Like this right here with hooks if you
remember from earlier in the course.
但现在我们要把整个阵列称为 " 神虎克 "
But right now we're just gonna grab
the whole array and call it themeHook.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then I'm gonna
wrap everything inside of here,
在 StrictMode 的内部。
inside of StrictMode here.
ThemeContext ，然后您说值 = themeHook。
ThemeContext and
then you say value = themeHook.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，现在我们在这里做了什么，对不起，你必须做
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now what we've
done here, sorry, you have to do
这两个 .Provider ， .Provider上的 ThemeContext 。
ThemeContext on both of these .Provider,
.Provider.
嗯。
Yeah.
>> Brian Holt: 因此在第 22 行和第 12 行引入
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So on line 22 and
line 12 there introduce
Themecontext.provider， >> Brian Holt: 因此
Themecontext.provider,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
我们在这里所做的一切
what we've done here is now
everything inside of here has
可作为全局应用提供此主题。
available as a global app
state this themeHook.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，我可以有两个不同的主题挂钩供应商，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, I could have two
different theme hook providers where they
可以具有搜索参数，并且详细信息具有不同的提供程序。
can have search params and
details have different providers.
它们可以有不同的价值。
And they could have these
value be different things.
所以实际上，你可以在上下文和
So there's actually a lot of flexibility
that you can do with context and
我从没用过
I just never use it.
所以我认为有用的唯一方法就是
So, the only thing that I find useful is
providing like the entire application with
一个全局应用程序状态，但是您可以执行一些 fanciness 。
a global application state but
there is some fanciness that you can do.